It will scare you out of your skull.
The Bone Snatcher is a science fiction, horror film directed by Jason Wulfsohn.
After miners disappear in the Namib Desert, some scientists find
their remains and the demonic creature that killed them.
Dr. Zack Straker, played by Scott Bairstow.
Mikki, played by Rachel Shelley.
Karl, played by Warrick Grier.
Titus, played by Patrick Shai.
Kurt, played by Andre Weideman.
Magda, played by Adrienne Pearce.
The Bone Snatcher is a 2003 British-Canadian horror film directed by Jason Wolfsohn
and starring Scott Bairstow, Rachel Shelley, and Adrienne Pearce.
The film is based on a screenplay by Malcolm Kohll and Gordon Render.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.